#### HARRY HAYDEN

7 Leysmill Close, Hinckley, LE10 0RU | 07817441977 | hrhayden12@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

I am a dedicated, organized and methodical individual. I have good interpersonal skills, am an excellent team worker and am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills. I am reliable and dependable and often seek new responsibilities within a wide range of employment areas. I have an active and dynamic approach to work and getting things done. With the ability to operate and maintain a wide variety of IT equipment with proven experience in both military and production environments.

### **EDUCATION**

Code Institute

Diploma in Full Stack Development	Ongoing
Wiltshire and Somerset College NVQ Level 3 Telecommunications	2014
Leicester College NVQ Level 2 Electrotechnical Technology Installation	2010
The Robert Smyth School 12 A-C GCSE inc Maths, English, ICT	2008

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Hivestack March 2022 - Present

# Platform Support Specialist EMEA

Provide high level technical support to clients across the EMEA and wider regions.

Answer and support clients in their technical requests.

Identify, troubleshoot and resolve technical issues related to the platform to ensure prompt resolution.

Diagnose and escalate issues to Engineering when appropriate.

Collaborate with teams when required.

Give feedback and insights to the relevant teams on features that would improve the overall customer experience.

Crane August 2018 - March 2022

# Software Support Coordinator

Manage corporate installations of Crane software and Web Services.

Be able to remote in and observe installations so can troubleshoot.

Support Crane Companies, Distribution Partners and End Users globally.

Be able to communicate with corporate IT departments on requirements and security

Act as expert on what operating systems and databases we should support

Customer facing, potential overseas travel and onsite installation

Generate customer software URS (User Requirement Specification)

Liaise with Engineering and subcontract software engineers on customer requirements

Commission software projects and training customers

Technical sales support

Testing Crane software and products and problem solving.

HARRY HAYDEN PAGE 2

#### Atlas Copco

**August 2017 – August 2018** 

<u>Software Service Engineer - Contracted by Jaguar Land Rover</u>

Responsible for providing both on-site and remote real-time technical support for critical IT and Network systems in a manufacturing environment. This includes the monitoring and maintenance of a LAN, including servers, network ports, cabling and associated client's hardware and software involved in the mass production of the customer's product. Working alongside different departments including Projects, Sales and Engineering to provide appropriate solutions to the customer's requirements. Conducting data, log file and system analysis to rectify performance and configuration issues. Maintain and update incident logs and deliver detailed incident reports to fit the customer's requirements.

Labwaste Ltd 2015 - 2017

## Logistics Manager

I started out as an ADR driver, driving vans and HGV vehicles around the country collecting hazardous waste and chemicals. After working for the company for a few months I was internally promoted to Logistics Manager. With this position came extended pressures and responsibilities. These include routing and briefing drivers each day on their daily routes comprising from 1 to 15 jobs a day across 15 drivers considering the costs and profit included in these jobs. Another aspect of the job is to contact the customers we service both via email and telephone. Ensuring the drivers complete daily vehicle checks and maintain their vehicles to a high standard. Although employed as Logistics Manager I do also partake in ensuring drivers and yardmen comply with the health and safety rules of our hazardous waste yard.

#### **ADR Network**

Primark Delivery Driver – HGV Class 2

2014-2015

Delivering between 100-800 parcels to single or multiple Primark stores across the UK.

### Disney Distribution Centre, Magna Park

Inventory Control

As part of the inventory control team I was responsible for locating and correcting Items that had been incorrectly scanned in or out of the distribution centre. Using the MS Excel spreadsheet I would keep control of stock inventory and make amendments to ensure our stock levels were always correct.

#### **HM Armed Forces (Army)**

### Communications Systems Operator

2010-2014

I ensured that the communications network was working well for soldiers and commanders on the battlefield. I engineered and operated digital radio systems and satellite communications. I performed routine safety checks on vehicles and equipment. Maintained and updated incident logs.

Electrician 2010

Waiter/Chef 2009

# INTERESTS/PERSONAL EXPERIENCES

Whilst being in the Armed Forces I have developed a lot of sporting interests and also experienced a wide variety of cultures. These included:

- Skiing Championships
- Army Football
- Army Athletics

HARRY HAYDEN PAGE 3

- Army Cross Country
- Army Triathlon

One of my most rewarding and memorable experiences is being deployed to Afghanistan and helping to run a busy Helicopter Landing Site. We did this with many other nations and it helped me develop an understanding of other cultures ways of life.

## **DRIVING LICENCES**

I hold the following licenses:

- Category C
- Category C+E
- DQC
- ADR 1-9 (Including Explosives and Radioactives)

### **ATTRIBUTES**

Enthusiastic

Familiar with project management
Familiar with Microsoft packages, Web Services, SQL and Asp.net
Able to write queries and support SQL Server Express
Familiar with Android OS and apps
Familiar with Servers and Client installations
VB scripting
Communication – Wi-Fi, Ethernet, Bluetooth, USB, RS232
HTTP and web-based systems
Team player
Familiar with MS Office and MS Project
Written and Verbal skills

#### **REFEREONCES**

Available upon request.